{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "authorize",
      "answer": "授權",
    },
    {
      "question": "ban",
      "answer": "禁止",
    },
    {
      "question": "bound",
      "answer": "束縛",
    },
    {
      "question": "captivity",
      "answer": "拘留",
    },
    {
      "question": "compulsory",
      "answer": "義務性的",
    },
    {
      "question": "convict",
      "answer": "宣告有罪",
    },
    {
      "question": "court",
      "answer": "法庭",
    },
    {
      "question": "defend",
      "answer": "辯護",
    },
    {
      "question": "forbid",
      "answer": "禁止",
    },
    {
      "question": "imprisonment",
      "answer": "監禁",
    },
    {
      "question": "jurisdiction",
      "answer": "權限",
    },
    {
      "question": "pledge",
      "answer": "誓言",
    },
    {
      "question": "oath",
      "answer": "宣誓",
    },
    {
      "question": "penal",
      "answer": "刑罰的",
    },
    {
      "question": "saddle",
      "answer": "馬鞍",
    },
    {
      "question": "trial",
      "answer": "試驗",
    },
    {
      "question": "veto",
      "answer": "否決",
    },
    {
      "question": "flee",
      "answer": "逃出",
    },
    {
      "question": "fine",
      "answer": "罰款",
    },
    {
      "question": "domineering",
      "answer": "專橫的",
    },
    {
      "question": "illegitimate",
      "answer": "非法的",
    },
    {
      "question": "violation",
      "answer": "違反",
    },
    {
      "question": "plead",
      "answer": "懇求",
    },
    {
      "question": "empower",
      "answer": "授權",
    }
  ]
}
